Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Nursing, Yale University, student records
1957-2013
RU 919
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
52.25
(55 boxes)
The records consist of student records and grade sheets of the Yale School of Nursing.
Yale University. School of Nursing
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 29-F (YRG 29-F), Student records of the Yale School of Nursing
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Yale School of Nursing, 2002-2013.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records and grade sheets of the Yale School of Nursing.
Nursing students; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. School of Nursing
- Student records for the Classes of 1959-1969, Accession 2003-A-039
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
  - Class of 1959
  - Class of 1960
  - Class of 1961
  - Class of 1962
  - Class of 1963
  - Class of 1964
  - Class of 1965
  - Class of 1966
  - Class of 1967
  - Class of 1968
  - Class of 1969
- Student grade sheets, 1994-2001; Accession 2003-A-040
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - 1994 fall (Box 1)
  - 1995 (Box 1)
  - 1996 (Box 1)
  - 1997 (Box 1)
  - 1998 (Box 1)
  - 1999 (Box 1)
  - 2000 (Box 1)
  - 2001 spring (Box 1)
- Student records for the Classes of 1970-1980, Accession 2008-A-041
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  - Class of 1970
  - Class of 1971
  - Class of 1972
  - Class of 1973
  - Class of 1974
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
  - Class of 1977
  - Class of 1978
  - Class of 1979
  - Class of 1980
- Student records, circa 1948-1999; Accession 2010-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - Advanced Program in Mental Health Nursing - grade sheets, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Student records for the Classes of 1981-1999, Circa 1977-1999; Accession 2013-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - American Nursing Credentials Center copies of letters - Grad '98, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 1343a)
- Student records for the Classes of 2000-2007, Accession 2014-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2088
  General
  The inclusive dates of the records range from 1996 to 2013 unless otherwise specified
  - 2000 Academic Files
  - 2001 Academic Files
  - 2002 Academic Files
    - Abstracts (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - 2003 Academic Files
  - 2004 Academic Files
  - 2005 Academic Files
  - 2006 Academic Files
  - 2007 Academic Files